I don't think he was trying to unite the country.
That's where we disagree, that's bullshit.
In fact, he divided the country further.
But intent doesn't really matter to my claim.
If he's releasing violent criminals,
it doesn't matter.
Wait, wait, wait, intent doesn't matter?
No, he's pro-crime and pro-criminal.
No, but that's a big indictment to say pro-crime.
That means he's for crime.
I'm confronted, well he is, because for example,
I gave an example.
No, no, no, it could be possible.
Can I finish?
Okay, sorry, forgive me.
Your friend earlier, your ally,
said where has he done stuff that's increased the crime?
I'm telling you, people have been pardoned
who have been convicted on multiple other crimes.
These people who we pardoned
had previous criminal records.
They were not just some folks chilling around
and go, we're against the takeover of our country,
we're opposed to rebellion.
A lot of these people were already hardened.
Criminals, militia members.
He looked at those people and said,
you know what, they've been convicted,
in many cases, by Republican judges,
but I'm gonna let them out.
Yeah, that makes you pro-criminal.
Can I ask you a question?
Is it possible?
Very much so.
And if Joe Biden had done it,
you'd be attacking him.
Sure, is it possible that their conviction
was part of the plea?
It's like, oh shit, I can't get out of this,
so I gotta take a plea deal.
Some of them, maybe.
A lot of them, maybe.
Others, we saw with our own lying eyes on tape,
battering police officers.
So I wanna eventually.
Did you watch live on January 6th, what happened?
To be completely honest, I'm pretty novice on this.
I'm more trying to target,
you're saying he's pro-crime,
and in my head, just thinking this logically,
let me finish, if I can finish for one second.
If thinking this, there's a possibility
that he might have had other reasons,
for example, unifying the country,
next chapter, right?
That that could have been the reason.
Therefore, it's not pro-crime,
there was other reasons.
I'm just saying, that's a possibility.
And I'm saying it's a possibility,
but I'm saying it's irrelevant,
because if you're releasing, knowingly,
releasing violent criminals out into the community,
pardoning, not just releasing,
then yes, you are being pro-criminal.
And I've interviewed police officers.
I don't know about that case, but I.
I've interviewed police officers
who have been assaulted, beaten,
had to retire from the police office,
broken bones.
Can I move really quickly?
Let me say this out, I'll finish very quickly.
I've interviewed these police officers.
They've been beaten by people
who they've then seen walk off the streets
and then carry on threatening them.
Yes, when Donald Trump is responsible for that,
you're definitely pro-crime.
Okay, I doubt a lot of the sources, but.
All right, pause, pause.
You doubt police officers
who testified to being assaulted?
You've been voted out by the majority.
Please return to your seat.
Thanks.